If I fell in love with you
要是我爱上了你
翻译，特效，压制: 布尔
字体: 思源宋体 SemiBold
Would you promise to be true
你能保证对我真心实意吗
And help me understand
帮我重新认识爱的含义
'Cause I've been in love before
因为我也曾坠入爱河
And I've found that love is more
我发现爱是复杂的
Than just holding hands
绝不是牵牵手那么简单
If I give my heart to you
要是我全心全意爱着你
学习音轨在简介中的原简介赞助页面中
I must be sure from the very start
打一开始我就必须确定
that you would love me more than her
你得爱我超过爱她
more than her
超过她
If I trust in you, oh please
要是我相信你的话 噢拜托
don't run and hide,
别跑掉也别躲着我
if I love you too, oh please
要是我也爱你 噢拜托
don't hurt my pride like her
别像对她那样伤害我的自尊
'Cause I couldn't stand the pain
因为我无法承受这种痛苦
And I would be sad
我会伤心的
If our new love was in vain
要是我们建立的爱情是徒劳的
So I hope you see that I
那样我仍希望你明白
would love to love you
我当初还是真的爱你的呀
And that she will cry
而她将会为此哭泣
when she learns we are two
当她知道了我俩的事的时候
'Cause I couldn't stand the pain
因为我无法承受这种痛苦
And I would be sad
我会伤心的
If our new love was in vain
要是我们建立的爱情是徒劳的
So I hope you see that I
那样我仍希望你明白
would love to love you
我当初还是真的爱你的呀
And that she will cry
而她将会为此哭泣
when she learns we are two
当她知道了我俩的事的时候
If I fell in love with you
要是我爱上了你
fell in love with you
我爱上了你